Finding Aid of the Dave Berkman Papers, 1958-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1958-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 347; 4.2 cubic ft. (5 boxes, including 38 audio cassettes) 1 videocassette 448 digital audio files (22 GB)
  - 2. Radio Broadcasts, 1991-2009
    - A. Media Talk, 1991-2006
      - Most Censored Stories of 2005, 12 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:46:37) (Electronic 79)
        With Peter Phillips, author, "The Top 25 Censored Stories"
      - Lobbying Power of NAB, 19 November 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:09) (Electronic 80)
        With Charles Layton, senior writer for AJR
      - Will Durst, 26 November 2004, 2 digital audio files (0:05:45 and 0:38:03) (Electronic 81-82)
        With Will Durst, political comedian
      - How Blogs are Changing Journalism, 03 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 83)
        With Henry Farrell, assistant professor of Political Science & International Affairs, George Washington University
      - Future of Network Nightly News, 10 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 84)
        With Brian Montopoli, Reporter for CJR Daily
      - United Church of Christ Ad Controversy, 17 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 85)
        With Gloria Tristani, managing communications director, United Church of Christ
      - Small Town Newspapers, 24 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:58) (Electronic 86)
        With Joe Karius, publisher of Ironwood Daily Globe
      - Review of the Media in 2004, 31 December 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:45:16) (Electronic 87)
        With Joe Strupp, senior editor, "Editor and Publisher"
      - Controversial Comic Strips, 07 January 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:13) (Electronic 88)
        With David J. Mehegan, features writer, Boston Globe
      - Women in the Sports Media, 14 January 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:15) (Electronic 89)
        With Joanne Gerstner, president, Association for Women in Sports Media
      - Drug Advertising, 21 January 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:35) (Electronic 90)
        With Linda Marsa, Mother Jones Reporter
      - Resignation of FCC's Chairman, Michael Powell, 28 January 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:54) (Electronic 91)
        With Bill McConnell, Sr Writer, Broadcasting & Cable Magazine
      - PBS Caving Into Indecency Crusade, 04 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:52:33) (Electronic 92)
        With Steve Behrens, editor for Current
      - High Schoolers & 1st Amendment, 11 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:52:01) (Electronic 93)
        With Gene Policinski, First Amendment Center Executive Director
      - Blame the Audience?, 18 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:29) (Electronic 94)
        With Evan Cornog, publisher, CJR
      - Film on Media & WMDs, 25 February 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:18) (Electronic 95)
        With Danny Schecter, filmmaker, "Embedded: Weapons of Mass Deception"
      - Bush Administration Control of Media, 04 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 96)
        With Lori Robertson, managing editor, American Journalism Review
      - Dan Rather's Career, 11 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:12) (Electronic 97)
        With Matthew Felling, media director, Center for Media & Public Affairs
      - Ethics of Fake News, 18 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:33) (Electronic 98)
        With Bob Priddy, chairman, Board of Directors, Radio/TV News Directors Association
      - State of the News Media, 25 March 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:55:36) (Electronic 99)
        With Tom Rosenstiel, director, Project for Excellence in Journalism
      - Presidential Candidates Coverage, 01 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:59) (Electronic 100)
        With Bryan Keefer, assistant managing editor, CJR Daily
      - Blonien's View of the Media, 08 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:40) (Electronic 101)
        With J.J. Blonien, editor, Wisconsin Conservative Digest
      - Rising Cable Rates, 15 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:09) (Electronic 102)
        With Susanna Montezemolo, policy analyst, Consumers Union
      - Wisconsin Historical Society Media Archives, 22 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:05) (Electronic 103)
        With Harry Miller, reference archivist, Wisconsin Historical Society
      - Global Warming Media Coverage, 29 April 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:58) (Electronic 104)
        With Ross Gelbspan, reporter, Mother Jones Magazine
      - Vast Left Wing Conspiracy, 06 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:48:37) (Electronic 105)
        With Bryon York, White House correspondent, National Review
      - Freedom of the Press Survey, 13 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:10) (Electronic 106)
        With Karin Karlekar, managing editor, Freedom of Press survey
      - Newsweek Gaffe, 20 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:58:01) (Electronic 107)
        With Joe Strupp, senior editor, Editor & Publisher Magazine
      - Faith Based News vs Mainstream, 27 May 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:00) (Electronic 108)
        With Mariah Blake, assistant editor, Columbia Journalism Review.
      - The Blanding of NPR, 10 June 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:54) (Electronic 109)
        With Scott Sherman, contributing editor, The Nation
      - Influence of Media Research Institute, 17 June 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:57) (Electronic 110)
        With Brian Montopoli, reporter, Columbia Journalism Review
      - Open Line, 24 June 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:43:45) (Electronic 111)
      - Bruce Murphy Interview, 01 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:03) (Electronic 112)
        With Bruce Murphy, senior editor, Milwaukee Magazine
      - The Jailing of Judith Miller, 08 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:46:01) (Electronic 113)
        With Matthew Felling, Media Director, Center for Media & Public Affairs
      - The Status of Black Journalists, 15 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:01) (Electronic 114)
        With Bryan Monroe, VP/Print, National Association of Black Journalists
      - Proposed Cable Decency Standards, 22 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:01) (Electronic 115)
        With Ted Hearn, D.C. news editor, Broadcasting & Cable
      - NewsMax Magazine, 29 July 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:12) (Electronic 116)
        With Christopher Ruddy, editor of NewsMax
      - None Dare Call It Stolen, 05 August 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:56) (Electronic 117)
        With Mark Crispin Miller, author of "Fooled Again"
      - The Impact of Peter Jennings, 12 August 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:16) (Electronic 118)
      - Open Line, 19 August 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:58) (Electronic 119)
      - Impact of John H. Johnson, 26 August 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:01) (Electronic 120)
        With Eugene Kane, columnist, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel
      - Media Coverage of Katrina Tragedy, 02 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:13) (Electronic 121)
      - The New TV Season, 09 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:57) (Electronic 122)
        With Joanne Weintraub, media critic, Milwaukee Journal-Sentinel
      - Pharmaceutical Industry & the Media, 16 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:52) (Electronic 123)
        With Trudy Lieberman, board president, Association of Health Care Journalists
      - Media Favors the Right on Evolution, 23 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:42) (Electronic 124)
        With Matthew Nisbet, assistant professor, Ohio State University
      - Media Effects on Children, 30 September 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:44) (Electronic 125)
        With Dr. Susan Villani, medical director of school programs, Johns Hopkins
      - Navasky Discusses 'The Nation', 07 October 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:41:55) (Electronic 126)
        With Victor Navasky, Publisher of The Nation
      - How TV Shapes Attitudes toward Race, 28 October 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:02) (Electronic 127)
        With Alan Nadel, literature & film professor, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute
      - Scooter Libby Indictment Coverage, 04 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:44:23) (Electronic 128)
        With Tim Cuprisin, media critic, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel
      - What's My Name Fool, 11 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:00) (Electronic 129)
        With Dave Zirin, senior writer at Basketball.com
      - Conservative View of Bush, 18 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:05) (Electronic 130)
        With Carl Limbacher, reporter for NewsMax
      - Coverage of White House Turmoil, 25 November 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:56:05) (Electronic 131)
        With Matt Felling, media director, Center for Media & Public Affairs
      - Bush's War on Al-Jazeera, 02 December 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:22) (Electronic 132)
        With Jeremy Scahill, independent journalist
      - Evangelical Radio, 09 December 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:45:04) (Electronic 133)
        With Adam Piore, reporter, Mother Jones Magazine
      - Media Saturation, 23 December 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:59) (Electronic 134)
        With Michael Bloxham, testing director, Center for Media Design, Ball State
      - Media in 2005, 30 December 2005, 1 digital audio file (0:51:55) (Electronic 135)
        With Joe Strupp, senior editor, Editor & Publisher
      - Censorship: The Family Guy, 06 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:02) (Electronic 136)
        With Steve Callaghan, writer & producer of Family Guy
      - Indictment of New York Times for Spying Story?, 13 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:04) (Electronic 137)
        With Harvey Silverglate, attorney & writer
      - Slashing News Departments for Profit, 20 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:54) (Electronic 138)
        With Douglas McCollam, Contributing Editor, CJR
      - Baby Einstein Effectiveness, 27 January 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:00) (Electronic 139)
        With Vicky Rideout, director, Study of Entertainment Media & Health/Kaiser Health
      - Tim Russert's Ethics, 03 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:27) (Electronic 140)
        With Joe Fontaine, columnist, Ripon College Days
      - Muhammad Cartoon Controversy, 10 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:05) (Electronic 141)
        With Gene Policinski, executive director, First Amendment Center
      - The New Journalism Revolution, 17 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:18) (Electronic 142)
        With Marc Weingarten, author, "Gang That Wouldn't Write Straight"
      - Open Line, 27 February 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:56) (Electronic 143)
      - 2006 Academy Awards, 03 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:44:56) (Electronic 144)
      - Open Line, 10 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:47:32) (Electronic 145)
      - McClatchy's Buying Knight Ridder, 17 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:08) (Electronic 146)
        With Steve Rendall, senior analyst, FAIR
      - Russ Feingold's Presidential Run, 24 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:54:41) (Electronic 147)
        With Chris Bower, blogger, mydd.com
      - Project for Excellence Annual Report, 31 March 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:08) (Electronic 148)
        With Dante Chinni, columnist, Christian Science Monitor
      - Katie Couric's Move to Evening News, 14 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:52) (Electronic 149)
      - What's Happening to TV?, 21 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:00) (Electronic 150)
        With Tim Cuprisin, TV critic, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel
      - Spanish Language Radio, 28 April 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:58) (Electronic 151)
        With Felix Gutierrez, executive director, Freedom Forum Pacific Coast Center
      - Administration Tries to Rein In Press, 05 May 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:36) (Electronic 152)
        With Joe Strupp, columnist, Editor & Publisher
      - White House Correspondents Dinner, 12 May 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:09) (Electronic 153)
        With Al Barger, Libertarian blogger
      - White House Woes, 19 May 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:02) (Electronic 154)
        With Chris Ruddy, editor, NewsMax
      - Book about Movie Terms, 26 May 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:06) (Electronic 155)
        With Richard Weiner, author, "The Skinny About Best Boys"
      - Spinning the Iraq War News, 02 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:57) (Electronic 156)
        With Daniel Schulman, assistant editor, Columbia Journalism Review
      - MySpace Controversy, 09 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:52) (Electronic 157)
        With Caz McChrystal, Law Student
      - Wisconsin Compliance w/ Public's Right To Know, 16 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:58) (Electronic 158)
        With Bill Lueders, president, Wisconsin's Freedom of Information. Council
      - Sob Sister Journalism, 23 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:51:47) (Electronic 159)
        With Stephanie Shapiro, feature writer, Baltimore Sun
      - FCC Indecency Fees, 30 June 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:43:44) (Electronic 160)
      - Last Show, 07 July 2006, 1 digital audio file (0:52:00) (Electronic 161)
    - B. Guest Hosting Appearances, 1997-2007
      - Late Night Television Talk Show Wars, September 1993, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 24)
        With Rick Kogan, television critic
      - Media Coverage of Labor, September 1993, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 24)
        With David Newby, AFL-CIO Wisconsin chapter
      - Gun Rights, 4 July 1997, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 25)
        With James Fendry, director, Wisconsin Pro-Gun Movement
      - Mike Tyson, 11 July 1997, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 25)
        With Art Taylor, Northeastern University Center for the Study of Sport in Society
      - Lesbian Minister, Presbyterian Church, 22 October 1999, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 26)
      - Constitution Party, 22 October 1999, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 26)
        Joseph Sobran, Vice-Presidential Candidate, Constitution Party
      - Racism in Milwaukee Media, 28 September 2000, audio cassette (Box 5, Audio 27)
      - Free State Project, 18 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:46:05) (Electronic 162)
        With Tim Condon, Libertarian Free State Project
      - Black Vote, 18 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:54:25) (Electronic 163)
        With David Bositus, Joint Center for Political & Economic Studies
      - Computer Voting Research, 29 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:19) (Electronic 164)
        With Aviel Rubin, Johns Hopkins Information Technology Institute
      - Religion divides Americans, 29 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:55:38) (Electronic 165)
        With Melissa Rogers, Pew Forum on Religion & Public Life
      - What Bush Needs to Win, 29 July 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:43:52) (Electronic 166)
        With John McAdams, Marquette University professor, political science
      - Democrats & Health Care Positions, 01 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:53:17) (Electronic 167)
        With John Schmid, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel economics writer
      - Election Coverage, 01 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:43:57) (Electronic 168)
        With Ken Goldstein, Wisconsin Advertising Project
      - Fundamentals of Extremism-Christian Right, 15 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:27) (Electronic 169)
        With Kimberly Blake, editor and co-author
      - Rising Support for 1st Amendment, 15 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:44:18) (Electronic 170)
        With Gene Policzinski, executive director, First Amendment Center
      - Defense of the Patriot Act, 22 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:14) (Electronic 171)
        With John Fonte, Hudson Institute senior fellow
      - Mandatory Celibacy, 22 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:53:47) (Electronic 172)
        With Father Collins, Roman Catholic Priest
      - Human Trafficking on U.S. - Mexico Border, 25 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:54:50) (Electronic 173)
        With Tim Padgett, Time Magazine Miami & Latin America Bureau Chief
      - US Asks UN for Military Assistance Resolution, 25 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:32) (Electronic 174)
        With Charles Hill, Yale Professor of International Security & UN Studies
      - Parents TV Council's Best & Worst Shows, 29 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:45) (Electronic 175)
        With Melissa Caldwell, director of research & publications, Parents TV Council
      - Owners of Harley-Davidsons, 29 August 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:22) (Electronic 176)
        With Jenn Danko, Shepherd Express reporter
      - Americans Want Free Time More Than Money, 01 September 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:33) (Electronic 177)
        With Diane Wood, executive director, Center for New American Dream
      - Labor Day: Brains not Brawn, 01 September 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:00) (Electronic 178)
        With Harry Binswanger, Ayn Rand Institute professor
      - Football TV coverage, 01 September 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:45:07) (Electronic 179)
        With Bob Wolfley, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel sports columnist
      - Wesley Clark Campaign, 26 September 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:49) (Electronic 180)
        With Thomas Mann, Brookings Institute, W. Averell Harriman Chair
      - Limiting Use of Plea Bargain, 26 September 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:42:47) (Electronic 181)
        With David Burnam, Syracuse, co-director of Transactional Act. Rec. Clearinghouse
      - Will Hillary Run?, 06 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:13) (Electronic 182)
        With Kathleen Parker, Orlando Sentinel columnist
      - Rush Limbaugh & ESPN, 06 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:44:29) (Electronic 183)
        With John Jackson, Chicago Sun Times reporter
      - Proposition 54 in CA, 06 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:45:10) (Electronic 184)
        With George Curry, editor-in-chief, National Newspaper Publishers Association
      - Rush Limbaugh Defender, 10 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:14) (Electronic 185)
        With Bill McGowan, author of "Coloring the News"
      - Wisconsin & Recalls, 10 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:44:55) (Electronic 186)
        With Mordecai Lee, UWM associate professor of governmental affairs
      - Detroit's Decline in Car Manufacturing, 31 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:11) (Electronic 187)
        With Micheline Maynard, author of "The End of Detroit"
      - What will Democrats sacrifice to Beat Bush?, 31 October 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:44:12) (Electronic 188)
        With Mitch Frank, national reporter at Time Magazine
      - "Do Not Spam" Legislation, 28 November 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:51:04) (Electronic 189)
        With Jamie Court, author, "Corporateering: How Corporate Power Steals Your Freedom"
      - Can Dean Be Beaten?, 22 December 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:33) (Electronic 190)
        With E.J. Dionne, Washington Post columnist
      - Discussion of Raised Terrorist Threat, 22 December 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:43:24) (Electronic 191)
        With Beau Grosscup, Cal State International Studies & Terrorism
      - Unwanted Xmas Gifts, 26 December 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:52:51) (Electronic 192)
      - Negative Youth Reaction to Bush-Bashing Stars, 26 December 2003, 1 digital audio file (0:44:08) (Electronic 193)
        With Damien Cave, writer for Salon.com
      - Listener's Most Important Stories of 2003, 02 January 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:50) (Electronic 194)
      - Democratic Presidential Primaries, 02 January 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:11) (Electronic 195)
        With Nat Hentoff, columnist, Village Voice
      - Profanity on Television, 19 January 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:50:49) (Electronic 196)
        With Melissa Caldwell vs Ron Collins, Parents TV Council vs author
      - MLK Open Line, 19 January 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:18) (Electronic 197)
      - Have Unions Lost Their Political Influence?, 06 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:24) (Electronic 198)
        With Robert Bruno, author, "Reforming the Chicago Teamsters"
      - Changed Your Presidential Candidate Choice?, 06 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:53) (Electronic 199)
      - Preserving the 'Sanctity of Marriage', 19 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:39) (Electronic 200)
        With Robert Knight, director, Culture & Family Institute /Concerned Women for America
      - Wisconsin Primary's Effect on Super Tuesday, 19 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:21) (Electronic 201)
        With Terry Neal, Washington Post columnist
      - The Skyrocketing Cost of Cable TV, 19 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:06) (Electronic 202)
        With Mark Cooper, director of research, Consumer Federation of America
      - Journalism Ethics & Rumors, 20 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:35) (Electronic 203)
        With Aly Colon, Ethics Group leader, Poynter Institute
      - Wisconsin Losing High Wage Jobs, 20 February 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:28) (Electronic 204)
        With Joel Rogers, Director, Center on Wisconsin Strategy
      - Media Censorship of Gory Photos, 06 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:28) (Electronic 205)
        With Joe Davidson, former Poynter Ethics Fellow
      - Juries & Jury Nullification, 06 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:00) (Electronic 206)
        With James Brosnahan, defense attorney
      - Outlook for 2004 Brewers Season, 06 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:28) (Electronic 207)
        With Bob Wolfley, sports columnist, Milwaukee Journal Sentinel
      - Media Coverage of 9-11 Hearings, 09 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:38) (Electronic 208)
        With Tim Graham, drector, Media Analysis at Media Research Center
      - Outcome of Milwaukee Mayoral Race, 09 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:01) (Electronic 209)
      - Corporate Profits & Labor Compensation Mismatch, 16 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:51:23) (Electronic 210)
        With Paul Harrington, associate director, Center for Labor & Market Studies, Northeastern University
      - Private Military Contractors, 16 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:56) (Electronic 211)
        With William Hartung, director, Arms Trade Project at the World Policy Institute
      - Interview w/ American Public, 22 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:34) (Electronic 212)
        With Steven Kull, director, Program on International Policy Attitudes, University of Maryland
      - Impact of Wal-Mart, 30 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:40:54) (Electronic 213)
        With Nelson Lichtenstein, professor of history, UC-Santa Barbara
      - Arlen Specter's Re-Election & Future for Moderate Republicans, 30 April 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:04) (Electronic 214)
        With Jennifer Duffy, Senate editor, The Cook Political Report
      - Why Sonia Gandhi Declined Prime Minister Position, 21 May 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:49:22) (Electronic 215)
        With Ravi Narasimhan, editor of The Hindu
      - Reinstate the Draft?, 21 May 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:43:13) (Electronic 216)
        With Stephen Budiansky, author, "Air Power: The Men, Machines & Ideas"
      - Kerry's Stand on Iraq, 28 May 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:52:48) (Electronic 217)
        With Richard Longworth, director, Global Chicago Center, Chicago Council on Foreign Relations
      - Why We Must Stay in Iraq, 28 May 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:16) (Electronic 218)
        With Joseph Klein, author, "The Foolish, The Feckless and The Fanatic"
      - Media Coverage of Reagan's Death, 16 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:50:58) (Electronic 219)
      - Mother Jones Political Poll, 16 June 2004, 1 digital audio file (0:44:31) (Electronic 220)